=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 23=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 23 =
Go. Don't mess it up again.
يذهب.  لا تعبث بها مرة أخرى.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't blow it up this time.
لن أفجرها هذه المرة.
Qiange. Eat something first.
Qiange.  تناول شيئًا أولاً.
I brought you some congee.
أحضرت لك بعض الكونجي.
I'm not hungry. You eat it.
انا لست جائع.  أنت تأكله.
Try a little.
جرب قليلا.
If you're too busy,
إذا كنت مشغولا جدا ،
I can feed you.
يمكنني إطعامك.
Try some.
جرب بعض.
Try it.
جربها.
Now, our selected designers
الآن ، المصممون المختارون لدينا
will elaborate on their designs.
سوف يشرح بالتفصيل تصاميمهم.
A successful design
تصميم ناجح
is not subjected to
لا يخضع ل
colors and forms visible to the audience.
الألوان والأشكال المرئية للجمهور.
Eyes are also...
العيون أيضا ...
Qianxun.
Qianxun.
What happened to her?
ماذا حدث لها؟
Find a doctor!
اعثر على طبيب!
Doctor!
طبيب!
Clear the way.
تمسح الطريق.
Don't jam together. Keep the air circulating.
لا تتكدس معًا.  حافظ على دوران الهواء.
Might be allergic.
قد يكون لديه حساسية.
Doctor,
طبيب،
I saw Qianxun have some porridge.
رأيت Qianxun لديها بعض العصيدة.
Could you check that?
هل يمكنك التحقق من ذلك؟
The congee contains something
يحتوي الكونجي على شيء ما
that was eaten by her with a large amount,
التي أكلتها بكمية كبيرة ،
leading to her allergic shock.
مما أدى إلى إصابتها بصدمة حساسية.
You're up.
أنت جاهز.
What's the result of the competition?
ما هي نتيجة المنافسة؟
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
What matters is that you're good.
ما يهم هو أنك جيد.
What happened to me?
ماذا حدث لي؟
Allergic shock.
صدمة الحساسية.
Someone slipped something in the congee I gave you.
شخص ما انزلق شيئًا في الكونجي أعطيتك إياه.
Sorry.
آسف.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
What's going on with the runway?
ما الذي يحدث مع المدرج؟
(The Gu's trapped in a marital fraud?) How could this happen?
(الغو محاصر في عملية احتيال زوجي؟) كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
I thought it's Qiange who has allergy.
(الغو محاصر في عملية احتيال زوجية؟) اعتقدت أن Qiange من لديه حساسية.
(Insider exposing Xia's daughters deceiving CEO) How come Qianxun has it too?
(من الداخل يفضح الرئيس التنفيذي المخادع لبنات شيا) كيف يحدث ذلك أيضًا في Qianxun؟
Could it be that...
(من الداخل يفضح الرئيس التنفيذي المخادع لبنات شيا) هل يمكن أن يكون ذلك ...
(Insider exposing Xia's daughters deceiving CEO) Oh, nothing.
(من الداخل فضح بنات شيا الرئيس التنفيذي المخادع) أوه ، لا شيء.
I was just blabbing.
كنت مجرد ثرثرة.
Don't take it serious.
لا تأخذ الأمر بجدية.
What are you going to do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
لا تقلق.  سوف أعتني بذلك.
Mr. Gu.
السيد.  قو.
What do you have to say about your wife's identity?
ماذا لديك لتقوله عن هوية زوجتك؟
Were you aware of the fact that the twins were switching identities?
هل كنت على علم بحقيقة أن التوائم كانا يتبادلان الهويات؟
In regard to this absurd action,
فيما يتعلق بهذا العمل العبثي ،
what is your final resolution?
ما هو قرارك النهائي؟
Do you have the plan of divorcing?
هل لديكم خطة الطلاق؟
Be quiet.
كن هادئاً.
Xia Qianxun.
شيا تشيان شون.
Our encounter was a misconstruction in the first place.
كان لقاءنا خاطئًا في المقام الأول.
I have known the whole story.
لقد عرفت القصة كاملة.
Therefore,
وبالتالي،
I decided to divorce you.
قررت أن أطلقك.